A Histogram is a column chart that measures the frequency of data in
直方图是一种柱状图 衡量的是数据在数据集中出现的频率
a data set and specifically groups numerical values into bins, we define.
具体而言 将值组合为我们定义的 bin (箱)
Recall that we previously created
之前 我们创建了一个柱状图
a column chart to compare counts of categories within a data set.
用于比较数据集中的类别数量
This kind of chart answers a question like,
这种图表可以回答类似于
how many players are there in each playing position in the league?
“大联盟中每个位置有多少名球员？”这样的问题
But what if we want to ask the question,
但是如果我们想知道
how many players made under $1 million in salary,
有多少球员的薪资不到 100 万美元
and between $1 and $2 million,
在 100 万到 200 万美元之间
and between $2 and $3 million in salary, et cetera?
在 200 万美元到 300 万美元之间 等等 该怎么办？
This kind of a chart is a histogram,
这种图表就是直方图
and the groupings we choose such as,
我们选择的分组
all salaries between $1 and $2 million and salaries between $2 and $3 million
例如在 100 万到 200 万美元、200 万美元到 300 万美元之间的薪资
are the bins.
就是 bin
There are two ways to do this in Excel.
在 Excel 中可以用两种方式绘制该图表
We'll start with a method that works on both Windows and
我们将先介绍在 Windows 和 Mac 上都可行的方法
Mac using the histogram tool in the analysis tool pack add-in.
即使用分析工具包插件中的直方图工具
Instructions for loading the analysis tool pack
你可以在使用入门说明中找到
add-in are given in the Getting Started instructions.
加载分析工具包插件的说明
The second way is a simple insert chart method available for Excel 2016 for PC.
第二种方式是 使用 PC 版 Excel 2016 中的简单插入图表方法
I'll show you that too.
我也会演示该方法
The tool pack histogram requires two columns of data.
工具包直方图需要两列数据
One for data you want to analyze and one for
一个是要分析的数据列
bin levels that represent the intervals for the bins.
一个是表示 bin 之间的组距
In this example, I'm starting at $1 million,
在此示例中 我从 100 万美元开始
then $2 million, et cetera,
然后是 200 万美元 等等
up to $15 million.
一直到 1500 万美元
When I create the histogram,
当我创建直方图时
the number of values in the salaries lists that are
薪资列表中低于 100 万美元的值数量
below $1 million will be in the first bin.
将位于第一个 bin 中
The numbers of salaries between $1 and $2 million will be in the second bin, and so on.
在 100 万到 200 万之间的薪资数量位于第二个 bin 中 以此类推
To create the histogram,
要创建该直方图
choose data analysis from the data menu on Windows or from the tools menu on Mac.
在 Windows 上从数据菜单中选择数据分析 或者在 Mac 上从工具菜单中进行选择
Choose histogram, which opens a dialog.
选择直方图 随即打开一个对话框
For the input range,
在输入区域
select the data from the salaries column.
选择薪资列中的数据
For the bin range,
在接收区域 (Bin range)
select the bin intervals you've created.
选择你所创建的组距
If you have a label at the top of your columns as I do here, click labels.
如果列的顶部有标题 就像我的这样 勾选“标志” (lable) 项
For the output options,
在输出选项中
select new worksheet and chart output,
选择新工作表以及图表输出
and press OK. Excel will analyze
点击确定
the list and create a count for the bins on a new worksheet,
Excel 将分析列表并在新的工作表上创建对 bin 的计数
and then create a column chart to match it.
然后创建一个与之匹配的柱状图
The second method is only available in Excel 2016 on Windows.
第二种方法仅适用于 Excel 2016 (Windows 版)
Just select your data and click insert,
选择你的数据并点击“插入”
recommended charts and choose the histogram chart.
“推荐的图表” 然后选择直方图
To configure details about the bins,
要配置 bin 的细节
right click the horizontal axis of the chart,
右击图表的横轴
click format axis and then click axis options.
点击设置坐标轴格式 然后点击坐标轴选项
The dialog provides options for choosing categorical data
该对话框提供了选择分类数据的选项
like the player positions or automatic for numerical data.
例如球员位置 以及针对值数据的“自动”选项
You can specify the number of bins which you might choose to experiment with a bit.
你可以指定你想要研究的箱数 (Number of bins)
If you choose bins that are too narrow,
如果选择的 bin 太窄
the result can be noisy.
结果可能噪声太多
On the other hand, too few bins will hide details.
另一方面 如果 bin 太少 就隐藏了一些细节
Here as always, think about what you're trying to learn and convey about the data,
和往常一样 思考下你要了解和传达关于数据的什么信息
and use that as your guide for making these determinations.
并据此作出这些判断
As with other charts,
和其他表格一样
design and layout can be further
选择图表后 可以在设计菜单中
customized from the design menu when the chart is selected.
进一步自定义设计和布局